This traditional Annovazzi hairpin
carries a certain secret.
When worn on a hand, it becomes a weapon
called a knuckle duster
that increases the force of blows.
Always a Catch!
Knight Captain
Episode 7
The Fists of the One That Got Away
Hey, Mimi.
Are you sure this is all you want
to bring back for the prince?
We have sheep and whole roast cows.
Those are both large animals.
I'll just take what
I can fit in the carriage.
But he'll eat through this in no time!
No, he won't!
But hunger ruins gains.
The prince isn't trying to build muscle.
Their relationship's back
to how it used to be.
Good.
What a tomboyish crown princess.
She's leaving? I'll miss her.
COME
Teo.
It's all right. I'll be back soon.
Really? Then I'll be a good boy and wait.
I'll escort you to your carriage.
Oh, no. He's too cute.
I wish I could take him with me.
That's a terrifying expression.
Take my hand, milady.
Yes, milord.
Let's go, future duke.
Open the door.
Thank you for the lovely escort.
You just need to train
at your own pace, okay?
Okay.
Take care.
Give our regards to the prince.
To Lady Maria's departure!
Take care!
Maria! Maria! Maria!
I'll be back soon.
Honestly, it's not like we'll
never see each other again.
Come to think of it, I wonder if
that village found their missing girl.
You mean Navarro Village?
What a kind lady.
This might actually work.
We're real lucky fer shore.
I wonder what happened after that.
We'll be in the area. Let's stop by.
What a lovely smell.
Hello.
Milady? What are you doing here?
I see. You haven't found her yet.
No.
And you have no idea where she went?
Actually, someone saw
Veronica, the chief's daughter,
getting into Count Nardi's carriage.
What? You mean...
Hey! Terrible news!
You're that noble lady.
Thank you again for helping us.
Did something happen?
I just went to check
on Count Nardi's mansion, and...
Just hand over the crops!
I told you to leave!
You think you can talk to us like that?
We'll report this to Count Vesentini.
They were arguing with
some nasty-looking guys.
Some thugs showed up at the mansion?
Who's Count Vesentini?
A customer who buys our
crops from Count Nardi.
So...
Count Nardi gathers up this village's
crops and sells them to Count Vesentini?
Yes.
Sounds like a dispute between counts.
This smells suspect.
What? Does something smell bad?
Oh, did I say that out loud?
I didn't mean it like that.
It must be our crops.
What?
This is what we grow.
It has a unique smell.
Let me see.
SNIFF
It stinks!
Doesn't it? This is all we
can grow in our poor soil.
It's processed into a spice.
But why? I smelled a pleasant aroma
when I entered the village.
We don't know why,
but when this plant is smelled
while flowering, the scent is like citrus.
You're right. That smells nice.
This is all our village has.
I wouldn't say that.
You must be very worried that a girl
went missing from this peaceful village.
Yes.
From what I gather, Count Nardi
must know something.
Yes. We think she was kidnapped.
So we're planning
to pay the count a visit.
Yeah. If those thugs are involved,
we gotta do somethin'!
I'll go with you.
Having a noble on your side
will make a difference.
Milady, that's not a good idea.
But I have to do something
after hearing all that.
Of course.
You would say that.
Thank you.
Who are you guys?
Get out of here.
I'm a member of the Annovazzi family.
I'd like to speak with the count.
You're some high muck-a-muck? Buzz off.
The count's not seeing anyone.
Buzz off?
I can't blame him for not knowing
the nobles of a little kingdom.
M-Milady?
Are you all right?
I'm fine. I expected this.
If we can't get through
the front gate, then...
We don't even know where the girl is.
What are you going to do?
In buildings like these,
captives are always held in
back rooms on the highest floor.
There.
Stay here and attract the guards
by causing a commotion.
Gather all the soldiers
to the first floor if you can.
You're going to enter by yourself?
It's too dangerous.
A brawny man breaking in
would raise suspicion.
I'll be able to hide myself.
Macchio, come help me climb.
Very well, milady. Just don't overdo it.
I'll be fine.
I've got this.
That said, this is for self-defense only.
I'd rather avoid violence.
As long as I avoid running into people...
H-Hello...
Hello.
Excuse me.
That was a surprise.
There was totally someone in there.
Well, whatever. I made it to the hallway.
I'll just keep going.
All clear. On to the next place.
Yeah. We haven't checked
the upper floors yet, right?
Right.
Two men on the stairs.
One man shirking his duties on the sofa.
Hey, when's the count coming back?
Who knows? It's been two months since
he went to the capital for a meeting.
It's really dragging on.
What? Count Nardi's been gone for months?
Then who kidnapped the girl?
Come on, man. Don't fart.
Pee-yoo!
What? Who are you?
What?
Wait, what?
That fart wasn't me!
Huh? What's all this noise?
This is your fault!
I acted without thinking, but I can't
let them think a lady passed gas.
Absolutely not.
Is the girl upstairs?!
I'd better hurry.
She must be on this floor.
Hey, who are you guys?
It's getting noisy downstairs.
Goffredo and the villagers
are doing a good job.
There are more servants over here.
I'd better stay hidden.
But then I can't use this.
If I crawl, I won't be ready
if the soldiers find me.
In that case...
Number 41, shuffling.
Number 41 Shuffling
It's a martial arts technique from
the far eastern art of "soo-mow."
But why is it a secret technique?
Because it looks a little embarrassing!
As a noble lady and young woman,
I don't want anyone to see me doing this.
Absolutely not.
What?
Hello to you!
Sorry. I couldn't let you go
after you saw that.
I'll put you in this storage room.
Um...
Who are you?
Toss
Are you Veronica of Navarro Village?
Y-Yes.
Great. I'm here to rescue you.
Are you hurt?
What? Rescue me?
Someone's coming. Stand back.
I refuse to marry you!
R-Rejected for marriage again!
Always a Catch!
Rejected for marriage again...
I've been rejected twice
for marriages I wasn't aware of.
Veronica, are you all right?
Yes. Who is she?
What? She's not Lady Ella?
Um, what's your name?
It's Mimi.
My apologies. I am Hugo Nardi,
Count Nardi's son.
A certain count is demanding
I marry his daughter
in exchange for buying our crops.
You mean Count Vesentini?
Yes.
So that's why you mistook me
for his daughter.
You should at least confirm
who you're speaking to
before calling off an engagement.
My heart already belongs to Veronica.
Hugo, you should marry Lady Ella
for the village's sake, too.
What are you talking about?
I can't imagine a future without you.
Hugo...
Veronica...
So, this wasn't a kidnapping?
Did the villagers ask you to come here?
I'm terribly sorry for the inconvenience.
I was actually planning to flee
with her while my father's away.
You mean you were going to elope?
A forbidden love! An illicit affair!
Two lovebirds put to the test!
I love it so much!
Um, Miss Mimi?
I'll protect you.
I won't allow anyone
to tear you lovebirds apart.
Let's table eloping and
reconsider pursuing another future.
Thank you. I appreciate the offer.
Veronica!
You're all right.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
I'm glad you're safe as well, milady.
Not that we were that worried.
Seriously?
Lord Hugo, terrible news!
The warehouse is under attack!
What?
Could it be?
Them again?
We're taking everything in the warehouse.
Count Vesentini will
buy it at a high price.
Stealing costs us nothing.
All the profits are ours to keep.
Hand over whatever you've got, too.
This important deal will
determine your future.
Lord Hugo, this isn't a deal.
You don't have to hand over
your precious crops.
Y-Y-You!
You again! What are you doing here?
Who is that woman?
Silence.
She's the future crown princess of Rubini.
I am Maria Annovazzi.
What?!
She's a genuine princess.
Oh, no. I didn't use your proper title.
It's fine. We're friends now.
We'll defeat these guys.
I want you two to be happy.
Lady Maria...
That's right, leave.
We don't need the count.
I'll find a new buyer.
I won't deal with you anymore.
Yeah. We're not giving you our crops.
Leave the goods and go.
Yeah, leave!
Get out of here!
Those crops are ours!
B-Boss, what should we do?
Idiots! Don't be scared!
Hey! How long does it take
to shut up one noble brat?
S-Sorry, boss. They're fighting back.
And that woman's the one
who got in our way the other day.
What?
Goffredo, Macchio.
He's no ordinary thug.
He's got a lot of experience
under his belt.
I've heard about you. I didn't
realize you're just a little girl.
What? She's the new princess of Rubini!
Show some respect!
Don't!
Damn villagers.
You've got guts to stand up to us.
Boys, get the goods out of here.
Wait!
You're smart enough to understand
what's going on, don't you?
If you want him to live,
you'll stay out of our way.
This is bad.
This way, sirs!
What? Knights of Rubini?
Unhand him!
Now!
Boss!
Are you all right?
Thank you, Princess.
What are you saying? I'm sorry
for putting you through that.
I hope nothing's broken.
Treat this man right away.
Understood.
Impressive as always, Lady Maria.
That was a good number 10.
Thank you. You came.
Yes. We rushed here after hearing
the plea from the villagers
who came to the royal castle.
We're glad yous made it in time.
And we're not the only ones who came.
Mimi, are you all right?
Prince Renato? What are you doing here?
Did you come to meet me?
Macchio and Goffredo,
let me introduce you.
Milady, watch out!
Move!
I can't reach him from here.
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
Renato!
Get out of the way!
Thirty-eight!
What?
Ouch...
Your Highness, are you all right?
Are you hurt?
No. I'm fine.
Seize him!
He's unconscious.
How...?
How did I do?
I've been secretly practicing
the number 38 you showed me
the morning you left.
But I only showed it to you
that one time.
His Highness punched a man
with his bare hand.
Lord Raimondo, pull yourself together.
I'm glad you're not hurt,
but please don't do that again.
That's right. If anything
happened to you, I...
I'm so glad you weren't injured.
Anyway, I had no idea
punching someone hurt this much.
Your Highness...
You have more physical and
political strength than anyone else.
Please remember that the pain
you inflict on others is far greater.
You must never forget that pain.
I'll keep in mind how heavy my fists are.
But you can also use that power
to protect people.
Thank you for coming
to save me, Your Highness.
Of course.
Translation: Sho Stifler
Timing: Mariana Martinez
Editing: Alicia Ashby
Quality Control: Ashley Barboza
Final Quality Control: Michelle Tymon
My little brother Teo loves meat
and is a good boy
who eats plenty of everything.
GLOW
I'm sure he'll grow up to be big.
Dad likes sweet things,
despite how he looks.
Next Time
The Secret  Date of the One That Got Away
Oh, I spoke my mind again.